Now, this algorithm is very simple. And conceptually,
现在，这个算法非常简单。从概念上讲，
I think it's, it's very clear how it works. But there are a number
我认为，它是如何运作的，这是非常清楚的。但是有一个数字
of tricky details and this is very typical of automatic memory management algorithms.
这是非常典型的自动内存管理算法。
And there's actually a serious problem with the mark phase. And, and this is also
事实上，标记阶段有一个严重的问题。还有，这也是
typical of, of garbage collection algorithms. Now, notice that we only run this
垃圾收集算法的典型。现在，请注意，我们只运行以下内容
algorithm when we are out of space, okay. So, the whole point is that we're garbage
算法，当我们没有空间的时候，好的。所以，关键是我们是垃圾
collecting because there's no more system memory available for allocating new
正在收集，因为没有更多的系统内存可用于分配新的
objects. And yet we have this to-do list, okay. And notice that the work list was not
对象。不过，我们有个待办事项清单，好吧。请注意，工作列表并不是
bounded in size. There was no guarantee about how many elements were going
在大小上有界限的。不能保证会有多少元素
to be on the to-do list. And I think, it's easy to see that, that data structure
出现在待办事项清单上。我认为，很容易看出，这种数据结构
could actually be fairly large, alright. And so, we can't just allocate a
实际上可能相当大，好吧。因此，我们不能就这样分配一个
fixed amount of space for the to-do list or reserve some constant amount of space.
为待办事项列表保留固定数量的空间，或保留一定数量的空间。
But we need to deal with the fact that we actually don't have any space at all when
但我们需要面对的事实是，当我们没有任何空间的时候
we get around to doing a garbage collect ion. Now, there is a trick that can be used
我们抽出时间来做一次垃圾收集。现在，有一个小把戏可以用来
to maintain the to-do list during the mark phase without having to use any extra
在标记阶段维护待办事项列表，而不必使用任何额外的
storage. And that is to do what is called pointer reversal. So, when a pointer is followed,
储藏室。这就是所谓的指针反转。因此，当跟随指针时，
it's going to be reversed to point back to its parent. And this is going
它将被反转，指向它的父级。这就是我们要做的
to allows us actually to track what elements or what objects in the heap still
允许我们实际跟踪堆中仍有哪些元素或对象
need to be processed without having to use any extra space. And let's just if you don't
需要在不使用任何额外空间的情况下进行处理。如果你不这么做的话
understand that I'm going to do an example in just a second. I wanna mention
请理解，我马上就要做一个例子了。我想提一下
a second problem as well and that is, you know, where is the free list stored? And this
第二个问题是，您知道，空闲列表存储在哪里？还有这个
is a little easier to see how that works. So, the free list consists of blocks
更容易理解它是如何工作的。因此，空闲列表由块组成
of memory. And, and we just use the space in these blocks to maintain the free
记忆中的一部分。而且，我们只是利用这些区块中的空间来保持空闲
list so perhaps the first word or something of the block of memory will contain
所以也许记忆挡路的第一个词或某个东西会包含
the size of the block and then the second word will point to the next block in
挡路的大小，然后第二个字将指向下一个挡路
the list, you know, something like that but we can use the space in the blocks themselves
列表，你知道，类似的东西，但我们可以使用区块本身的空间
to maintain the free list. And so, now let's come back to this pointer reversal
以维护空闲列表。所以，现在让我们回到指针反转这一点
idea. Let's say that we have some objects, okay, and we want to track reachability,
好主意。假设我们有一些对象，好的，我们想要跟踪可达性，
okay, and we can't maintain the to-do list, all right in a separate data
好的，我们不能把待办事项列表保存在单独的数据中
structure. And so how are we going to do that? Well, well, here's the idea when
结构。那么我们要怎么做呢？好吧，好吧，我是这么想的
we change colors. So, we're doing to come in here and we're going to mark this first
我们换颜色。所以，我们要进来这里，我们要首先标记这一点
object. Let's say this is reachable from the root and now that this is the root the
对象。假设这是可以从根到达的，现在这是根
first object. And now we're going to follow the pointers in this object and let's
第一个对象。现在我们将跟随此对象中的指针，让我们
say this is one here, this one here is the first pointer in the object. So, we're
假设这里是1，这里的这个是对象中的第一个指针。所以，我们要
going to follow it and then we're going to reverse it. We're going to have it
跟随它，然后我们要反转它。我们将拥有它
point back to the parent. So, now we will mark this object and then we'll follow
指向父级。所以，现在我们将标记此对象，然后我们将跟随
the pointers in, in this object, okay. And as we go down, we'll have this pointer
这个对象中的指针，好的。当我们往下走的时候，我们会看到这个指针
point back and then we'll mark this object. And now, we got no point ers
向后指，然后我们将标记此对象。现在，我们没有得分者
in this object and so we need to go back and process any pointers that weren't covered
在这个对象中，所以我们需要返回并处理任何未覆盖的指针
in the object set that we that we have already seen, okay. And how do we find
在我们已经看到的对象集中，好的。我们怎么才能找到
our way back? Well, that's what the pointer reversal was for. So, we could follow
我们回去的路？嗯，这就是指针反转的目的。所以，我们可以跟着
the blue arrow back here, as we come back, we'll restore the original pointer.
后面的蓝色箭头，当我们回来的时候，我们将恢复原来的指针。
So, we'll get rid of the reversed pointer. There are no more pointers in this
所以，我们要去掉反转指针。这里没有更多的指针了
object either so we'll go back one more object and now, of course, this pointer
对象，所以我们再返回一个对象，当然，现在这个指针
will go away and we'll restore the original pointer, alright. And now, we're
会消失，我们会恢复原来的指针，好吗？现在，我们正在
in this object and we see there was a second pointer that we haven't followed yet,
在这个对象中，我们看到还有第二个指针，我们还没有跟随它，
okay. And, and then we'll follow it and we'll reverse it and we'll follow the
好吧。然后，我们将跟随它，我们将反转它，我们将遵循
other pointer from that, reversing it, and, and then we'll mark these two objects,
另一个指针，颠倒过来，然后我们会标记这两个物体，
when we get down to this object and we discover there are no additional pointers,
当我们深入到这个对象时，我们发现没有额外的指针，
we'll be able to use this, these blue arrows here to work our way back and
我们就可以用这个，这些蓝色箭头往回走，
we'll restore the red arrows as we walk back up through the objects. So, essentially
当我们重新穿过这些物体时，我们将恢复红色箭头。所以，从本质上讲，
the point of reversal does is it helps us maintain the stack for a depth
反转的要点是它帮助我们在一定深度内保持堆栈
for search of the graph. So, if you're doing adept for search of the graph and you
用于搜索图表。所以，如果你做的是熟练的搜索图表，而你
want to be sure that you cover all the notes that are reachable then you have to
想要确保您覆盖了所有可以到达的便条，那么您必须
be able to do the back tracking. And the, the reversed pointers allow us to do that
能够进行回溯。反转的指针让我们可以做到这一点
[cough]. There's one more tiny issue here with the reversed pointers. So, notice that
[咳嗽]。这里还有一个关于反向指针的小问题。所以，请注意，
there's a little bit of a problem. So, I want to talk about reversing pointers
有一点小问题。所以，我想谈谈反向指针
and let me draw two new objects here just to illustrate the point. Let's say,
让我在这里画两个新的物体来说明这一点。比方说，
I have a, a pointer from this object to that object. So, when I cross over, to
我有一个，一个从这个对象指向那个对象的指针。所以，当我超度的时候，
the object that is pointed to, what does it mean to reverse this pointer? Well the,
指向的对象，反转此指针意味着什么？那么这个，
you know, the space where the pointer is actually in this object, there's no space
你知道，指针实际在这个物体中的空间，没有空格
necessarily for the pointer at all in, in the object that I'm going to. And so, in fact,
对于指针来说是必要的，在我要去的对象里。所以，事实上，
what's going to happen let's say this was part of a chain of objects, okay.
接下来会发生什么，让我们假设这是一系列物体的一部分，好的。
And, and this problem is easily solved, the issue is just off by one problem. So,
而且，这个问题很容易解决，这个问题只是由一个问题引起的。所以,
I have, I have space in this object for a pointer and I can change that pointer. I don't
我有，我在这个对象中有一个指针的空间，我可以改变那个指针。我没有
know if I even have any pointers in this object yet, alright. So, let's say this
我知道我在这个对象中有没有任何指针，好的。那么，让我们这样说吧
is part of a chain of objects, okay, and that I've walked down this chain to, to
是一系列物件的一部分，好的，我沿着这个链条走到，到
this particular object. So, as I pass over to this third object with I, the pointer
这个特殊的物体。所以，当我使用指针i传递到第三个对象时
that I will reverse is this one and I will make it point back to the previous
我要颠倒过来的是这一条，我会把它指向前一条
object, okay. And then I'm just going to remember this particular object,
反对，好的。然后我就会记住这个特别的物体，
you know, I'll keep the pointer to this particular object in a register. So, I'll
你知道，我会把指向这个特定对象的指针保存在一个寄存器中。所以，我会
keep the last pointer at reversed in a register. An, and a pointer to the last object
将寄存器中的最后一个指针保持在反转位置。和指向最后一个对象的指针
that I came from in a register and then when I go on to another object, I will
我是从一个登记处出来的，然后当我转到另一个物体时，我会
use the pointer that I'm traversing in the current object to point back to the
使用我在当前对象中遍历的指针指向
parent of the previous object, okay. So, it's just a off by one problem, I need one
上一个对象的父级，好的。所以，这只是一个问题，我需要一个
register here to hold on to the previous object that I visited and then I can reverse
在此注册以保留我访问的前一个对象，然后我可以反转
pointers back up to their parents and grandparents. Alright, to summarize the
回溯到他们的父母和祖父母身上。好的，总结一下
discussion of mark-and-sweep. Space for a new object is going to be allocated
关于标记和清扫的讨论。将为新对象分配空间
from the free list, little typo there. And we're always going to pick a block, we always
从免费列表上看，这里有个小打字错误。我们总是会选挡路，我们总是
have to pick a block from the free list that is large enough to hold the object
我必须从免费列表中选择一个足够大的挡路来容纳该对象
that we're allocating. And in an area of the size that we need is going to
我们正在分配的。在我们需要的面积内
be allocated from that block and then the leftovers is to be put back on the free list.
从那个挡路中分配，然后剩下的就会被放回免费的名单上。
So, let's say the free list has a block, let's say it has 100 bytes and then
那么，假设空闲列表有一个挡路，假设它有100Bytes，然后
we need an object that has 50 bytes in it. So, what will happen is that this block will
我们需要一个包含50个字节的对象。那么接下来会发生什么呢，就是这个挡路
get split up. We'll use this first half, the first 50 for the object and then
分头行动。我们将使用前半部分，前50个用于对象，然后
this other part the leftover will get put back on to the free list. And the result of
剩下的这一部分将被重新放回免费列表中。其结果是
that kind of strategy where we, we have to find blocks that are big enough but then
这样的策略，我们，我们必须找到足够大的区块，但是
we might not use the entire block is that mark-and-sweep can fragment the memory.
我们可能不会使用整个挡路是因为标记和清除可以碎片化记忆。
We might wind up with lots of little bits of leftover memory maybe nothing
我们可能会留下很多零碎的记忆，也许什么都没有
big enough to actually hold an object. And these blocks, these little tiny
大到足以容纳一个物体。而这些积木，这些小小的
blocks might be scattered all over the place. So, it's important actually, for
积木可能散落在各处。所以，事实上，这很重要，因为
mark-and-sweep to also merge blocks whenever possible. So, it's merge free blocks,
只要有可能，也可以标记并清除以合并块。所以，它是自由合并的块，
when possible. So, basically when the sweep phase is working on the free list.
如果可能的话。所以，基本上当扫描阶段在空闲列表上工作时。
It needs to recognize when it has two adjacent blocks of memory that will be
它需要识别它何时有两个相邻的内存块
immediately adjacent to each other in memory. So, if I have two blocks that are
在内存中彼此紧邻。所以，如果我有两个街区，这两个街区
contiguous, what I really want to do is to merge them into one big block and just have
连续的，我真正想做的是把它们合并成一个大挡路
one entry in the free list. That's a counteract fragmentation of memory. Now, one
空闲列表中的一个条目。这是对记忆的一种抵消的碎片化。现在，一个
big advantage and perhaps the biggest advantage of mark-and-sweep is that objects
标记和清扫的最大优点，或许是最大的优点是，对象
are not moved during garbage collection. And that means I don't have to
在垃圾收集期间不会移动。这意味着我不需要
update the pointer objects. Object stay put, they don't move as part of garbage collection.
更新指针对象。对象保持不动，它们不会作为垃圾回收的一部分移动。
And what this means is it's actually possible to adapt mark and sweet,
这意味着实际上有可能改编马克和斯威特，
for languages like CNC++. So, in CNC++, pointers are exposed to the programmer so
用于像CNC++这样的语言。因此，在CNC++中，指针向程序员公开，因此
programmers can, can manipulate pointers and test pointers and so you can't move objects
程序员可以，可以操纵指针和测试指针，所以你不能移动对象
in CNC++ because the pointer is part of their semantics. The pointer address,
在CNC++中，因为指针是它们语义的一部分。指针地址，
I should say, is part of their semantics. But it is actually possible and
我应该说，是他们语义的一部分。但这实际上是可能的，而且
people actually have done it to build conservative or, you know, variations of a
人们这样做实际上是为了构建保守的或，你知道的，变体的
mark-and-sweep garbage collection for C++ precisely because the objects don't move.
C++的标记和清除垃圾回收正是因为对象不会移动。